Atlantic States Legal Foundation; Records apap311
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Publications, 1966-2009; Undated; 2; 47.82 cu. ft.
  - Serials, 1971-2009; 2.1
    - American Indian Program, 1986 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Arbor Day News, 1983-1994 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 9-10)
    - ARC News, 1992 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 11)
    - ARCS Update, 1991-1994 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Arizona Water Resource, 1992-1996 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 13)
    - Around the World, 1990-1991 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 14)
    - Arroyo, 1993-1996 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Ava News, 2000 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 16)
    - Bay Bulletin, 1992 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Bay Journal, 1991-2009 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 18-25)
    - Beyond Borders, 2007-2008 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Birdscope, 1994-1996 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 1)
    - Birth Defect Prevention News, 1988-1991 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 2)
    - Bringing Back the Bay, 1998; 2001-2004 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 3)
    - Buckhorn Bulletin, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Business & Energy, 2001 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Canary Calls: The Hardrock Reform Reporter, 1994-1995 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Center for Biodiversity and Conservation Newsletter, 1999 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Centerline, The, 1991-2008 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Central New York Environment, Undated (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 9)
    - Central New York Labor Religion Coalition Report, 1998 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Chemical & Engineering News, 1991-1994 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 11-22)
    - Chemicals in Progress Bulletin, 1996 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Chemistry in Britain (1-4 of 12), 1977-1985 (Box 2 (2-Publications), Folder 24-27)
    - Chemistry in Britain (5-12 of 12), 1977-1985 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 1-8)
    - Choices, 1993 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 9)
    - Citizen's Clearinghouse for Hazardous Wastes, 1986 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Citizen's Mining Information Network Mine Monitor, 1992 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Clean Communities of Central New York, 1997 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Clean Water Action Council of Northeast Wisconsin, The, 1988-1992 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 13)
    - Clearwaters, 2004 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 14)
    - Clementine, 1989-1995 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 15-16)
    - CNY Newsline, 2001-2004 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Coastal Connection, 1992 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 18)
    - Coastal Connections, 2003-2009 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Coastal Management Program, New York State, Undated (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 20)
    - Coastal Society Bulletin, 1990 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Coastlines, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Common Ground, 1991-2005 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 23-24)
    - Community and Worker Right to Know News, 1991 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Community Plume, The, 1991 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Conservationist, The, 1994 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 27)
    - Conservation Law Foundation (C.L.F.), 1992; 1993 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 28)
    - COPE Quarterly, 1993 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 29)
    - COPPE Quarterly, 1991-1992 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 30)
    - Cornell Center for the Environment: Environmental Update, 1989; 1992-1997 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 31)
    - Cornell Waste Management Institute, 1989-1998 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 32)
    - Crest, The, 2007 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 33)
    - CRUW News, 1996-1997 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 34)
    - Current: The Journal of North Country Action (1 of 2), 1987-1993 (Box 3 (2-Publications), Folder 35)
    - Current: The Journal of North Country Action (2 of 2), 1987-1993 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 1)
    - Defending the West, 1996-2007 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 2)
    - Delaware Conservationist, 1979; 1984-1990 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 3-5)
    - Detroit River Remedial Action Plan, 1990-1991 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Dialogue on Hamilton Harbor, 1988 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Directions, 1981; 1982; 1994-2009 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 8)
    - DOMES: Deep Ocean Mining Environmental Study, 1977 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 9)
    - Don't Waste New York Newsletter, 1990-1991 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Down & Dirty, 1999-2001 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Dredging Research, 1991-1994; 1998 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Dredging Research Technical Notes, 1992-1994 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 13)
    - Dreissena Polymorpha Information Review, 1992 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 14)
    - Earth First!, 1990 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Ecorecovery, 1994-1995 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 16)
    - EDF Letter, 1992-1994 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Eighty-Niners, The: Mining Conservation Directory, 1989 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 18)
    - E-law Update, 1992-1999 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Elements, The, 1975-1979 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 20-22)
    - Emergency Management Times, 1997-1998 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Energy Statement, 2004 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Environment, New York State, 1979-2002 (Box 4 (2-Publications), Folder 25-29)
    - Environmental Action, 1979-1995 (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 1-5)
    - Environmental Advocate, The, 1998-2005 (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Environmental Business Association of New York State, 1998-2001 (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Environmental Effects of Dredging, 1991-1994 (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Environmental Justice Watch, 1997 (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 9)
    - Environmental Law, Northwestern School of Law of Lewis & Clark College, 1999; 2000 (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Environmental Law Alert, 1995-1996 (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Environmental Monitoring, Evaluation, and Protection Program NEWS, 2003; 2004 (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Environmental Notice Bulletin (1-9 of 64), 1982-1999 (Box 5 (2-Publications), Folder 13-21)
    - Environmental Notice Bulletin (10-26 of 64), 1982-1999 (Box 6 (2-Publications), Folder 1-17)
    - Environmental Notice Bulletin (27-43 of 64), 1982-1999 (Box 7 (2-Publications), Folder 1-17)
    - Environmental Notice Bulletin (44-60 of 64), 1982-1999 (Box 8 (2-Publications), Folder 1-17)
    - Environmental Notice Bulletin (61-64 of 64), 1982-1999 (Box 9 (2-Publications), Folder 1-4)
    - Environmental Observer, 2005 (Box 9 (2-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Environmental Policy Center, Colorado School of Mines, 1993 (Box 9 (2-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Environmental Research, 1971 (Box 9 (2-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Environment Reporter, 1990; 1991 (Box 9 (2-Publications), Folder 8)
    - EPA Journal, 1978-1987 (Box 9 (2-Publications), Folder 9-10)
    - ESA Today, 2000-2002 (Box 9 (2-Publications), Folder 11)
    - ESPA Express, The, 1980-2009 (Box 9 (2-Publications), Folder 12-14)
    - Estuary News, 1997-2002 (Box 9 (2-Publications), Folder 15)
    - E-Train News, 1996-2006 (Box 9 (2-Publications), Folder 16-17)
    - Everyone's Backyard, 1989; 2002; 2003 (Box 9 (2-Publications), Folder 18)
    - Examiner, The, 1991 (Box 9 (2-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Examiner, The New York State Solid Waste, 1996-2006 (Box 9 (2-Publications), Folder 20)
    - Facts to Act On, 1990; 1993 (Box 9 (2-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Farming Alternatives, 1995 (Box 9 (2-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Federal Geographic Data Committee Newsletter, 2001; 2002; 2005 (Box 9 (2-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Fieldwork, 1996 (Box 9 (2-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Fight to Save Alaska, The, 1982 (Box 9 (2-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Finger Lakes Institute, 2005-2007 (Box 9 (2-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Fish and Wildlife Reference Services Newsletter, 1980-2003 (Box 9 (2-Publications), Folder 27-30)
    - Fluoride Report, The, 1994 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 1)
    - Focus Conservation Fund, 2004 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 2)
    - Focus Greater Syracuse, 1997; 1998 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 3)
    - Focus on International Joint Commission Activities, 1988-2009 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 4-5)
    - Focus on Pesticides, 1997; 1998 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Forest Science Review, 2005 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Forum, The, 2000-2003 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Friends of the Buffalo River, 1990; 1991; 1993 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 9)
    - From the Ground Up, 1988-2004 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 10-12)
    - FSDWAC for Environmental Concerns, 1990 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 13)
    - Fund Facts, 1997 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 14)
    - Genesee/Fingerlakes Regional Review, 2004-2009 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Global News, International Center of Syracuse, 2002; 2004; 2006 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 16)
    - Grand Cal Currents, 1987; 1990 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Grassroots, 1988 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 18)
    - Great Lakes Aquatic Habitat News, 2002 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Green Action, 1996 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 20)
    - Green Drummer, The, 1993-1995 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Green Fire Alert, 2003-2004 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Green Fire Report, The, 1991-2003 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 23-24)
    - Green Guide, The, 1994-1996 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Greenings, 2008 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Green Sheet, The, 1996-2003 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 27)
    - Green Watch, 2004 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 28)
    - Hazardous Waste News, 1985-1986 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 29)
    - Hazardous Waste Outlook, 1990; 1992 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 30)
    - Healthy School Network News, 2000-2002 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 31)
    - Helping Small Business Succeed Through Pollution Prevention, 2003 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 32)
    - Hoosier Environmental Council Boardwatch, 1986-1989; 1990; 1992 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 33)
    - Hoosier Environmental Council HNF Bulletin, 1989 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 34)
    - Hoosier Environmental Council Monitor, 1987-1993 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 35)
    - Highlander Reports, 1987-2008 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 36-38)
    - Highlands Voice, The (1-2 of 3), 1995-1999 (Box 10 (2-Publications), Folder 39-40)
    - Highlands Voice, The (3 of 3), 1995-1999 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 1)
    - Home Range, The, 1997 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 2)
    - Illinois EPA: The condition of Illinois Water Resources 1972-1996 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 3)
    - Illinois Natural History Survey Publications, 1971; 1977; 1980; 1988 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Illinois Natural History Survey Reports, 1986-2008 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 5-8)
    - Impact, 1990 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 9)
    - Indian Law Resource Center, 1999 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Inform Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Information Exchange, The, 1998; 2000; 2001 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 12)
    - Inside ESF, 1997-2004 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 13)
    - InSite, 1992 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 14)
    - Institute for Conservation Leadership, 1999-2001 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 15)
    - Intercoast Network, 1996 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 16)
    - International Association for Energy-Efficient Lighting Newsletter, 1998-2000 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 17)
    - International Council on Metals and the Environment, 1994 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 18)
    - Israel Environment Bulletin, 1998-2007 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 19-20)
    - Journal of Pesticide Reform, 1994 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Kestral Newsletter, The, 1991-1992 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Knothole, 1998 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Lake Erie Connection, 1996; 1997 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Lakefront Today, 2001 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Lake Ontario Lakewide Management Plan, 1998-2008 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 26-27)
    - Lake Ontario Monitoring Program, 1993 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 28)
    - Lake Superior Binational Program, Undated (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 29)
    - Land and Water, 1986-2002 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 30-33)
    - Land Steward, The, 1995-1999 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 34)
    - Land Stewardship Letter, The, 1989-1993 (Box 11 (2-Publications), Folder 35-36)
    - Land Stewardship Update, 1990 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 1)
    - LAW Notes, 1990-1992; 1996 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 2)
    - LCARA News, 1989; 1991-1992 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 3)
    - Leadership Link, 2003 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 4)
    - LEAF, 2001-2002 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Leaf, The, 1988 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Leaf Briefs, 1991-2000 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Leaflet, 2000-2008 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Legislative Commission on Water, 2003 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 9)
    - Level News, 1996 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Living Bird, 1992-1996 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 11-13)
    - LOCI News, 2008 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 14)
    - Logbook of C2P2, 1997; 2000 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 15)
    - L.U.S.T. Line, 1985-2001 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 16-18)
    - Marsh Lander, 2004-2008 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Marsh Monitoring Program Newsletter, 2003; 2004 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 20)
    - Maryland Law Review, 1988 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Masinaigan, 1998-2004 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 22-23)
    - Masinaigan Supplement, 1999; 2001 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Mineral Industry Surveys, 1998 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Mineral Resources Newsletter, 1994 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Missouri Resource Review, 1993 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 27)
    - Mississippi Times, 1994 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 28)
    - MPC News, 1999; 2000 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 29)
    - Monthly Bulletin of Lake Levels for the Great Lakes (1-4 of 8), 1983-2009 (Box 12 (2-Publications), Folder 30-33)
    - Monthly Bulletin of Lake Levels for the Great Lakes (4-8 of 8), 1983-2009 (Box 13 (2-Publications), Folder 1-4)
    - Monthly Water Level Bulletin Great Lakes and Montreal Harbor, 1990; 1991; 1995; 1996 (Box 13 (2-Publications), Folder 5)
    - National Association of Railroad Passengers News, 1997-2009 (Box 13 (2-Publications), Folder 6)
    - National Weather Alliance Report, 1988-1990 (Box 13 (2-Publications), Folder 7)
    - National Hazards Observer, 1989-1995 (Box 13 (2-Publications), Folder 8-9)
    - Native Voices, 1998-2005 (Box 13 (2-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Natural Resources & Environment, 1990-1992 (Box 13 (2-Publications), Folder 11-12)
    - Natural Resources Register, 1984-1990 (Box 13 (2-Publications), Folder 13-15)
    - New Catalyst, The, 1992-1993 (Box 13 (2-Publications), Folder 16)
    - New England River Basins Commission Publications, 1975-1981 (Box 13 (2-Publications), Folder 17-20)
    - New England River Center Bulletin, 1980-1985 (Box 13 (2-Publications), Folder 21)
    - New Publications of the Bureau of Mines, 1992-1995 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 1)
    - Newsletter from the Hudson River PCB Reclamation Project, 1981 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 2)
    - Newsline, Adirondack Park Agency, 1986 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 3)
    - Nexus, 1993 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Nonpoint Source News-Notes, 1995 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 5)
    - North American Mining, 1997-1998 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Northeast Indian Quarterly, 1986 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Northern Perspectives, 1979-1985 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 8-9)
    - Northwest Nuggets, 1994 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 10)
    - New York Environmental News, 1976-1988 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 11-16)
    - Open Space, 2005 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Oswego River Remedial Action Plan Citizen's Committee Newsletter, 1988 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 18)
    - Our Toxic Times, 2006 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Outdoor California, 1992 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 20)
    - Pennsylvania Osprey, The, Undated (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Pens, Letters, Action, 1996 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Pesticides and You, 1982 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Pieces, 2005 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Pinelander, The, 1988-1992 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Preserve Appalachian Wilderness, Undated (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 26)
    - Public Justice, 1992-1996 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 27)
    - Resource Law Notes, 1989-1996 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 28)
    - Resources, 2006 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 29)
    - Revision Reporter, 1998 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 30)
    - River Voices, 2003 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 31)
    - Sea Grant Today, 1982 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 32)
    - Sierra, 1994 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 33)
    - Sierra Club Atlantic Chapter Iroquois Group Newsletter, 1974 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 34)
    - Silicon Valley Toxics Commission, 2007-2008 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 35)
    - Silicon Valley Toxics News, 1989 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 36)
    - Small Flows, 1995; 1996 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 37)
    - Southern Environmental Law Center, 1986-1993; 1995 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 38)
    - Southern Resources, 1991-1996 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 39)
    - Springboard, 2003; 2005 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 40)
    - State Watershed Leader, 1997-1998 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 41)
    - Stop Newsletter, 1987-1989 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 42)
    - Stream Notes, 2004 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 43)
    - Syracuse Water Newsletter, 1992-1995; 1998 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 44)
    - Taking Root, 2007; 2008 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 45)
    - Technical Information Project, 1992 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 46)
    - TIPS, 1987-1994 (Box 14 (2-Publications), Folder 47-48)
    - TLPJ Newsletter, 1990; 1995 (Box 15 (2-Publications), Folder 1)
    - Today's Chemist at Work, 1995-2003 (Box 15 (2-Publications), Folder 2-7)
    - Touching Bases, 1991 (Box 15 (2-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Toxics in Your Community, 1989-2002 (Box 15 (2-Publications), Folder 9-11)
    - Toxics Law Reporter, 1987-1988 (Box 15 (2-Publications), Folder 12-15)
    - Toxic Substances Control Newsletter, 1980-1983 (Box 15 (2-Publications), Folder 16)
    - Trustees for Alaska, 1989; 1991; 1993 (Box 15 (2-Publications), Folder 17)
    - Tug Hill Commission Newsletter, 1973-1986 (Box 15 (2-Publications), Folder 18)
    - Tulane Environmental Law Journal, 1998 (Box 15 (2-Publications), Folder 19)
    - Update of the Rural Coalition/Coalición Rural, 1996 (Box 15 (2-Publications), Folder 20)
    - UNEP CEPNews, 1995 (Box 15 (2-Publications), Folder 21)
    - Voice for Peace, The, 1992 (Box 15 (2-Publications), Folder 22)
    - Waste Line, 1989 (Box 15 (2-Publications), Folder 23)
    - Water Bulletin, New York State DEC, 1989; 1993 (Box 15 (2-Publications), Folder 24)
    - Watermark, 2005 (Box 15 (2-Publications), Folder 25)
    - Water Works, 1998; 2007 (Box 15 (2-Publications), Folder 26)
    - West Coast Environmental Law (1 of 3), 1992-2009 (Box 15 (2-Publications), Folder 27)
    - West Coast Environmental Law (2-3 of 3), 1992-2009 (Box 16 (2-Publications), Folder 1-2)
    - Western Environmental Law Center, 2006-2009 (Box 16 (2-Publications), Folder 3)
    - West Virginia Environmental Council, 1991 (Box 16 (2-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Wetland Journal, 1998 (Box 16 (2-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Wetlands Research Program Bulletin, The, 1994 (Box 16 (2-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Whole Farm Planner, The, 1997-2004 (Box 17 (2-Publications), Folder 1)
    - Wild Earth, Undated (Box 17 (2-Publications), Folder 2)
    - Wild in New York, 1992-1994 (Box 17 (2-Publications), Folder 3)
    - Wild Oregon, 1994 (Box 17 (2-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Wild Resource Conservation Fund Keystone Wild Notes, 1986-1988 (Box 17 (2-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Workbook, The, 1990; 1992 (Box 17 (2-Publications), Folder 6)
    - World Resources Institute Climate Notes, 2000 (Box 17 (2-Publications), Folder 7)
  - New York Publications, 1966-2007; Undated; 2.2
    This series contains reports and other official publications about issues affecting New York State. Federal, state, county and city governments and their agencies, including the Environmental Protection Agency or the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration, published the majority of these reports. Universities and non-profit organizations issued a smaller number. For reports specifically written by the New York State Department of Environmental Conservation, please see Series 2, Subseries 3.
    The publications discuss many environmental topics, such as hazardous waste or marine and coastal life. There are publications which analyze specific geographic areas, including the Long Island Sound, Lake George-Upper Hudson and the St. Lawrence River. As the Atlantic States Legal Foundation is based in Syracuse, there are a number of general reports and comprehensive planning documents about that city. Files also may contain supplemental materials related to the respective report such as an accompanying cover letter or news release.
    - Agricultural Labor Markets in New York State and Implications for Labor Policy, Final Report, 1991 May (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 1)
    - American Native Centers: Guidelines for Leadership in the Nineties, 1990 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 2)
    - An Analysis of New York's Timber Resources, 1984 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 3)
    - Analytical Critique of "Summary Consultants Report Relationship of Brining Operation in the Tully Valley to the Behavior of Groundwater and Geological Resources", Undated (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 4)
    - Analyzing New York State Streams for Possible Inclusion in the State Wild, Scenic, and Recreational River System, 1974 September (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 5)
    - Annual Evaluation of the New York State Hazardous Waste Site Remediation Program, 1989 January (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 6)
    - Annual Evaluation of the New York State Hazardous Waste Site Remediation Program, 1990 January (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 7)
    - Annual Evaluation of the New York State Hazardous Waste Site Remediation Program, 1991 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 8)
    - Annual Evaluation of the New York State Hazardous Waste Site Remediation Program, 1994 January (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 9)
    - Annual Evaluation of the New York State Hazardous Waste Site Remediation Program, 1995 (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 10)
    - Annual Evaluation of the New York State Hazardous Waste Site Remediation Program, 1996 January (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 11)
    - Annual Evaluation of the New York State Hazardous Waste Site Remediation Program, 1999 March (Box 1 (2-Publications), Folder 12)